▶ ComponentsPane & Evidence-Backed Component Inspector
  ✔ initializes with demonstration dataset of 12 connections and 48 bolts (total 60) (5.5718ms)
  ✔ selects components and exposes multi-view evidence bindings (3.4549ms)
  ✔ filters inventory by discipline, category, and search query (2.8517ms)
  ✔ supports ad-hoc trade additions and removals without corrupting component hierarchy (6.255ms)
  ✔ resets demonstration inventory cleanly on user command (6.3481ms)
  ✔ persists inventory mutations and reloads them via store persistence actions (3.4075ms)
  ✔ failed restores set inventoryPersistenceError and preserve unreadable data in storage (3.6497ms)
  ✔ hierarchical category filtering allows fastener filter to show all 48 bolts under their parent connections (3.883ms)
  ✔ verifies evidence drawing document before sheet navigation and flags unimported plans (3.536ms)
  ✔ dynamically flags unresolved engineering properties and updates RFI metric (3.6803ms)
✔ ComponentsPane & Evidence-Backed Component Inspector (43.8278ms)
▶ Evidence-Backed Component Inventory Schema (xray.component-inventory/v1)
  ✔ proves multi-view deduplication: 1 physical bolt appearing on plan, section, and detail (9.1579ms)
  ✔ solves the 12 connections * 4 bolts = 48 bolts problem deterministically (11.1085ms)
  ✔ isolates display marks: renaming B1 does not mutate stable IDs or break evidence links (0.9338ms)
  ✔ propagates assembly rule updates deterministically: changing 4 bolts to 6 bolts yields 72 bolts (8.6679ms)
  ✔ captures unresolved properties explicitly without hallucinating missing values (0.4352ms)
  ✔ rejects duplicate physical components sharing the same stableIdentifier even with different instance IDs (0.7707ms)
  ✔ preserves surviving components in place (retains custom display mark, section evidence, review, and revision 3) when assembly rule updates from 4 to 6 bolts (0.9036ms)
  ✔ updates rule-derived properties (e.g. M20 to M24, and unresolved embedment requirement) across all surviving components while preserving custom marks and evidence (5.0137ms)
✔ Evidence-Backed Component Inventory Schema (xray.component-inventory/v1) (37.9369ms)
▶ assembly rule reconciliation
  ✔ clears resolved rule requirements while retaining component-specific flags and evidence (5.231ms)
  ✔ advances materially changed components and marks their previous review stale without losing annotations (5.3015ms)
  ✔ requires re-review when missing requirements or rule-derived positions change (11.0618ms)
✔ assembly rule reconciliation (21.802ms)
▶ Component Inventory Persistence (xray:component-inventory:v1)
  ✔ round-trips exact validated inventory via storage (22.776ms)
  ✔ returns not-found when storage has no entry for the job (0.1847ms)
  ✔ fails closed and rejects corrupted JSON without crashing (0.1593ms)
  ✔ fails closed on schema version mismatch or invalid schema structure (0.1467ms)
  ✔ preserves previous valid snapshot if a subsequent write fails (5.5494ms)
  ✔ clears component inventory cleanly (3.9355ms)
✔ Component Inventory Persistence (xray:component-inventory:v1) (33.8278ms)
▶ inventory restore protection through real store actions and autosave
  ✔ preserves unsupported-version bytes through hydration, edits, autosave, explicit save and retry (5.2973ms)
  ✔ preserves invalid-json bytes through hydration, edits, autosave, explicit save and retry (3.5691ms)
  ✔ preserves invalid-schema bytes through hydration, edits, autosave, explicit save and retry (5.3185ms)
  ✔ unblocks only after a successful restore and persists the next edit across reload (9.7426ms)
  ✔ keeps recovery blocked if explicit demo replacement fails, then permits a successful replacement (9.9937ms)
  ✔ reports ordinary write failures and retries without treating them as failed restores (2.0061ms)
✔ inventory restore protection through real store actions and autosave (36.8493ms)
ℹ tests 33
ℹ suites 5
ℹ pass 33
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 292.9779
