{"method":"Fast CDP hot-socket declarative opcode batch; fail-fast; reactive readiness","browserSandbox":"enabled launch configuration verified against listening process and CDP; see sandbox diagnostics","iterations":1,"completedOps":58,"plannedOps":58,"elapsedMs":19140.8072,"verdict":"PASS","limitations":["Browser-level CDP is host authority, not a worker capability","No clipboard, download-content, OS process, secret or network-egress isolation proof","Development browser run; native package and production build not qualified by this campaign"]}
