✔ stock packages round up; unit weight differs from full-package weight (2.4068ms)
✔ decimal bulk units avoid spurious extra packs while partial packs still round up (0.1643ms)
✔ empty and unknown material list cannot report a complete zero total (0.284ms)
✔ weight can be specified without packing dimensions; package weights need capacity (0.1557ms)
✔ a stock quantity specified in kg is already a weight; no density is inferred (0.43ms)
✔ duplicate stock codes/IDs, invalid quantities and missing sources are rejected (0.8292ms)
✔ edits advance revision and reject a stale material editor (0.366ms)
✔ CSV preserves quantities, escaping, unknown blanks and source identity without formulas (0.3056ms)
✔ validated v1 upgrade preserves existing rows/reviews/stock and does not write on restore (2.5178ms)
✔ malformed v1 and invalid v2 material collections fail closed (0.7388ms)
✔ CSV parser handles BOM, CRLF, embedded commas/newlines and doubled quotes (1.1577ms)
✔ new exported CSV round-trips formula escapes and literal apostrophes losslessly (6.6262ms)
✔ template, unknowns and all supported units import without inferring numbers (0.6298ms)
✔ CSV rejects duplicate codes/headers, unknown columns and other drawing identity (1.0483ms)
✔ invalid CSV fails the entire import with record-specific errors (6.2507ms)
✔ CSV additions preserve counts; explicit updates retain IDs and advance changed revisions (1.0733ms)
✔ a changed local session or stored snapshot cannot be overwritten by an old CSV preview (2.4104ms)
✔ backup roundtrip and legacy exports retain notes, counts, references and IDs (6.3601ms)
✔ unsupported, foreign, extra or corrupt backup data is rejected (0.9581ms)
✔ restore preview remaps same-drawing project, resets review and shows removals (0.4745ms)
✔ explicit backup restore archives unreadable saved bytes before releasing recovery lock (0.6377ms)
✔ archive write failure prevents restore, and primary write failure preserves saved bytes (1.0779ms)
✔ restore refuses changed saved bytes and existing recovery archive IDs (0.7093ms)
ℹ tests 23
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 23
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 176.5592
