✔ independent oracle accepts dimensioned fixture with actual stairwell void (2.378ms)
✔ oracle detects courtyard filled (0.3001ms)
✔ oracle detects duplicate overlapping floor (0.1491ms)
✔ oracle detects stairwell covered (0.1735ms)
✔ oracle detects disconnected wall (0.2069ms)
✔ oracle detects incorrect storey (0.1651ms)
✔ oracle detects courtyard roofed (0.149ms)
✔ detailed stage does not award absent stairs, openings, pond, planters or site (0.3362ms)
ℹ tests 8
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 8
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 68.93
